Exercise 12-6, pick a peak. Repeat the following paragraph and words after me.
Bold-faced elements represent the E sound. The IH is only marked with underscoring.
People who pick peaks weekly seem to need to appear deep
in order to be distinguished from mere pea pickers. Peter, a champion peak-picker,
thought he'd be even neater if he were the deepest peak-picker in Peoria, Phoenix,
and New Zealand.
On his peak peak-picking week, though, Peter, a peak-picker's peak-picker,
realized that he was not deep. This is not easy for a peak-picker to admit, and it
pitched Peter into a pit of peak-picking despair.
He was pitiful for three weeks, and then lifted himself to hitherto unrevealed
personal peaks.